export const data = [
  {
    question: "What is the capital city of Bangladesh?",
    option1: "Chittagong",
    option2: "Khulna",
    option3: "Dhaka",
    option4: "Rajshahi",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the largest mangrove forest in Bangladesh?",
    option1: "Sundarbans",
    option2: "Lawachara National Park",
    option3: "Ratargul Swamp Forest",
    option4: "Madhupur Forest",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the national language of Bangladesh?",
    option1: "Urdu",
    option2: "Bengali",
    option3: "Hindi",
    option4: "English",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which city is known as the commercial capital of Bangladesh?",
    option1: "Sylhet",
    option2: "Chittagong",
    option3: "Rangpur",
    option4: "Barisal",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the currency of Bangladesh?",
    option1: "Rupee",
    option2: "Taka",
    option3: "Dollar",
    option4: "Pound",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which river is the longest in Bangladesh?",
    option1: "Jamuna",
    option2: "Padma",
    option3: "Meghna",
    option4: "Brahmaputra",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "In which year did Bangladesh gain its independence?",
    option1: "1947",
    option2: "1971",
    option3: "1981",
    option4: "1990",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the national flower of Bangladesh?",
    option1: "Rose",
    option2: "Lotus",
    option3: "Water Lily",
    option4: "Sunflower",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the national sport of Bangladesh?",
    option1: "Football",
    option2: "Cricket",
    option3: "Kabaddi",
    option4: "Hockey",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which mountain range is located in southeastern Bangladesh?",
    option1: "Himalayas",
    option2: "Hills of Chittagong",
    option3: "Garo Hills",
    option4: "Khasi Hills",
    ans: 2,
  },
];
